baplc.com 2015-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Legal | British Airways -

### British Airways is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information.

We’ve written this Privacy Policy to let you know how we use your personal information. In it, we explain the types of personal information we collect, how we collect it, what we use it for and who we may share your personal information with.

Below is a **high level summary** of the Privacy Policy, setting out the most important points. [View our full Privacy Policy (updated July 2014)](http://www.britishairways.com/information/legal/privacy-policy?).

This Privacy Policy comes into effect from 22 July 2014 and replaces our [previous Privacy Policy](http://www.britishairways.com/information/legal/privacy-policy/privacy-policy-2012). This Privacy Policy applies to all information we process about you in connection with your relationship with us as a customer or potential customer, including where you have a British Airways Executive Club account with us.

Please [contact us](http://www.britishairways.com/travel/askbainter/public/en_gb) if you would like to find out more about any matters to do with this Privacy Policy.

## High level policy

### What this Privacy Policy covers

This Privacy Policy covers all personal information about you that we collect, use and otherwise process in connection with your relationship with British Airways as a customer or potential customer. By “Personal Information” we mean information about you where you are, or could be, identified, such as your name and contact details, your travel arrangements and purchase history and information about your access to our websites.

### When do we collect personal information?

We collect personal information about you whenever you use our services (whether services provided directly by us or by other companies or agents acting on our behalf), when you travel with us, when you use our websites, or when you use our call centres or mobile applications.

### What types of personal information do we collect?

We collect personal information about you, about your travel arrangements, about how you use our services and about how you use our websites, call centres and mobile applications. This may include information that you provide to us directly or through companies or agents we work with, as well as information which we collect when you use our services.

### What do we use your personal information for?

  * To provide the travel and other services you have asked us to provide.
  * To personalise your travel experience.
  * To communicate with you about the travel and other services you have asked us to provide.
  * To provide you with marketing and offers from us (where we have your permission to do so).
  * To improve our services.
  * For security purposes.

### Who do we share your personal information with?

Your personal information may be shared within the group of companies controlled by our parent company, International Consolidated Airlines Group SA (IAG), for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy which includes British Airways Plc, Iberia LAE SA Operadora Unipersonal, British Airways Holidays Limited and Avios Group (AGL) Limited.

In order to facilitate your travel arrangements, we will often need to share your personal information with third parties including other airlines and airport operators, customs and immigration authorities, travel agents involved in making your travel arrangements and our customer loyalty partners, such as when you transfer between airlines or use a hotel to earn Avios. We also share your personal information with third parties who deliver services either to you or to us, such as companies that provide airport assistance or marketing agencies.

We do not sell personal information to third parties, and we only allow third parties outside the British Airways Group to send you marketing information where we have your permission to do so.

### How we look after the policy

We will keep this Privacy Policy under review and notify you of any changes by posting the revised policy on ba.com, to take effect as soon as it is posted.

## Detailed policy

Last updated: July 2014  
© British Airways Plc
